<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Water Monitor</string>
    <string name="bad_popup">Your water quality is bad!</string>
    <string name="good_popup">Your water quality is good!</string>
    <string name="ok_popup">Your water quality is ok!</string>
    <string name="Nitrates_popup">Nitrate is an inorganic compound that occurs under a variety of conditions in the environment, both naturally and synthetically.</string>
    <string name="NitratesHealth_popup">Nitrate is regulated in drinking water primarily because excess levels can cause methemoglobinemia, or "blue baby" disease. Short-term exposure to drinking water with a nitrate level at or just above the health standard of 10 mg/l nitrate-N is a potential health problem primarily for infants.</string>
    <string name="NitratesSuggestion_popup">Nitrate does not normally cause health problems unless it is reduced to nitrite. The suggestion value is 10 mg/l nitrate as a maximum.</string>
    <string name="Cyanide_popup">Cyanide is produced by the decomposition of some plants, can be present in some foods and water.</string>
    <string name="CyanideHealth_popup">Cyanide is very poisonous and ingesting high levels of cyanide may cause breathing difficulties, convulsion, loss of consciousness, brain and heart damage, or even coma and death.</string>
    <string name="CyanideSuggestion_popup">The World Health Organisation recommends that drinking water contain less than of 0.08 mg/L of cyanide and people should not consume water with a cyanide concentration above 0.5 mg/L for more than 5 days.</string>
    <string name="Organic_popup">Bacteria are typically single-celled microorganisms that can cause health problems in humans, animals or plants, despite many form’s ability to aid in water pollution control.</string>
    <string name="OrganicHealth_popup">Legionella,a bacteria found naturally in water, thrives in warm waters; this bacteria in water is a health risk if aerosolized (e.g., in a shower or air conditioning system) and inhaled, resulting in a type of pneumonia known as Legionnaires disease.</string>
    <string name="OrganicSuggestion_popup">Some disinfection technologies include: UV technology, chlorine, chloramine and ozone can effectively remove bacteria.</string>
    <string name="Description">Crystal Quest® Nitrate Removal + SMART Single Countertop Water Filter System is dependable and built to last for years. This counter top system installs in seconds and sits on the counter top for water on demand. Quick and easy to use, stylish, convenient, and effectively removes NITRATE and hundreds of contaminants from water.</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
</resources>
